WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -
What have you done?
All done.
Not so bad, was it?
See?
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Is there, Nancy?
Why don't you take a seat?
No!
Nancy, just stay with
me. Stay with me, okay?
Whatever you guys are doing, hurry up!
Steve says you need to hurry!
- Yeah? No shit!
- We're trying. We can't find anything.
- What is all this shit?
- What are you even looking for?
Madonna, Blondie, Bowie,
Beatles? Music! We need music!
This is music!
Son of a...
God!
Nancy.
What are you doing?
It's not time for you to leave.
Now that you've seen where I've been...
... I would like very much to show you
where I am going.
Take a seat, Nancy.
I...
want you to tell
Eleven.
I want you to tell her
everything you see.
No!
- Tell her...
- No!
... everything.
No!
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
It's okay. I'm here.
I'm right here.
What's going on there?
Get the power back on!
Tell him that the
prisoners are contained...
and that you're working on the power.
Tell him!
And that door there, where does it lead?
To... to cell block two...
No cell blocks!
I need a safe way out of here.
Guess you got my message, huh?
Oh, no, I just have always
wanted to visit the Soviet Union.
With Murray.
You two getting along?
He's the Starsky to my Hutch.
I thought you were dead.
Thought I lost you.
I did lose you.
For eight months.
We had a funeral.
Anybody show?
Are you kidding?
You're the hero of Hawkins.
It's true.
Yeah, I always felt I'd be
easier to like when I was dead.
How about El?
She's good.
She misses her dad.
We all do.
Uh, I hate to interrupt,
but apparently, they can climb too.
Lower your weapons.
Lower your weapons!
Don't shoot!
Stop!
The hell is that?
Please tell me they don't have
another one of those things.
You can't go in there!
It's dangerous!
Oh my God.
The hell are they doing?
Hey.
Found something.
- Think this'll lead us outta here?
- I give it a hundred to one odds.
And one, two, three.
Again. One, two, three.
Pulse is dropping.
One-fifty now. BP's 160...
How do you feel?
Can you hear us?
Eleven. Can you hear us?
No, leave her.
Hi, Jane.
Holy shit, dude. Check it out.
I didn't know they expanded into Nevada.
Watch out, Domino's.
Your dominoes are gonna fall.
How far is Nina from Vegas?
From Vegas?
Um, as long as Suzie's
coordinates are right,
about another 90 miles. Why?
Well, once we save her, El,
we should stop on the way back.
El could make us, like, super
rich, and we'd never have to work.
We could just play D&D and
Nintendo for the rest of our lives.
Yeah. Totally.
We're gonna make it,
Mike. She's gonna be okay.
Yeah, I know. I... I know she is.
But... But what if after
all this is over, she...
sh... she doesn't need me anymore?
No, o... of course
she'll still need you.
She'll always need you, Mike.
I keep telling myself that, but I...
I don't believe it.
I mean, she's special.
She was born special.
Maybe I was one of the
first people to realize that.
But the truth is, when I
stumbled on her in the woods,
she just needed someone.
It's not fate. It's... It's not
destiny. It's just simple dumb luck.
And one day she's gonna realize
I'm just some random nerd
that got lucky that Superman
landed on his doorstep.
I mean, at least Lois Lane
is an ace reporter for the
Daily Planet, right? But...
- Sorry.
- No.
No, i... it's so stupid, given
everything that's going on.
It's just... I... I
don't know, I just...
Uh...
You're scared of losing her.
Can I show you something?
This is amazing.
Did you paint this?
Yeah. Yeah. I mean...
I mean... I mean, El asked me to.
She commissioned it, basically.
I mean, she told me what to draw.
Anyway, my point is,
see how you're leading us here?
You're guiding the whole
party, inspiring us.
That... That's what you do.
And see your coat of
arms here? It's a heart.
And I know it's sort of on the nose,
but that's what holds
this party together. Heart.
Because, I mean, without
heart, we'd all fall apart.
Even El. Especially El.
These past few months, she's
been so lost without you.
It's just, she's so different
from other people, and...
... when you're...
when you're different,
sometimes...
... you feel like a mistake.
But you make her feel like
she's not a mistake at all.
Like she's better for being different.
And that gives her the
courage to fight on.
If she was mean to you
or she seemed like she
was pushing you away,
it's because she's scared of losing you,
like you're scared of losing her.
And if she was going to lose you,
I... I think she'd rather
just get it over with quick.
Like ripping off a Band-Aid.
So, yeah, El needs you, Mike.
And she always will.
Yeah?
Yeah.
After the attack,
you fell into a coma.
Like One, you had pushed
yourself beyond your limit.
And it very nearly destroyed you.
But that is where your
similarities ended.
What you displayed that day
was beyond anything I'd ever imagined.
A potential I'd only dreamed of.
But when you awoke,
something had been lost.
Your memories,
along with whatever else you'd
found within yourself that day.
But I knew then, just as I knew today,
that your powers had not been lost.
They just needed a spark.
But that day,
you awakened something else.
A doorway to another world.
I always thought that
Henry was out there,
hiding in the darkness.
I didn't know for sure,
not beyond a feeling.
Until now.
He's claimed three victims so
far, and when I saw the eyes,
I knew... I knew that was him.
He was sending us a message,
letting us know he's back.
That's when I came to see you.
My friends.
Well, we... we haven't risked contact,
but, as far as we know,
they're... they're all safe.
But I'm not gonna lie to you, Eleven.
Your friends are in terrible danger.
With each victim he takes,
Henry is...
chiseling away at the barrier
that exists between our two worlds.
"Chiseling"?
Imagine, if you will,
the barrier between our worlds is a...
concrete dam.
Henry is putting cracks in this dam.
Cracks in dams
create pressure.
Left unchecked,
the pressure will build.
And build.
And eventually, it will
reach a breaking point.
And the dam will burst.
And when that happens,
Hawkins will fall.
Well, that went very well, I thought.
You eased her into it, nice and
gentle, just like we talked about.
Not ominous at all.
He showed me
things that haven't happened yet.
The most awful things.
I saw
a dark cloud
spreading over Hawkins.
Downtown on fire.
Dead soldiers.
And this...
giant creature
with... a gaping mouth.
And this creature wasn't alone.
There were so many monsters.
An army.
And they were coming into Hawkins.
Into our neighborhoods.
Our homes.
And then...
he showed me my mom.
And Holly.
Mike.
And they...
they were all...
Okay, but... he's just
trying to scare you, Nance.
Right? I mean...
I mean, it's not real.
Not yet.
But there... there was something else.
He showed me gates.
Four gates.
Spreading across Hawkins.
And these gates, they looked like
the one outside of Eddie's trailer,
but... they didn't stop growing.
And this wasn't the Upside Down Hawkins.
This was our Hawkins.
Our home.
Four chimes.
Vecna's clock.
It always chimes four times.
Four exactly.
I heard them too.
He's been telling us
his plan this whole time.
Four kills.
Four gates.
End of the world.
If that's true...
he's only one kill away.
Oh Jesus Christ. Jesus Christ.
Try 'em again. Try 'em again.
- Anything?
- No.
Rang a few times, then
went to busy signal.
Maybe you punched it wrong. Try again.
- I didn't punch it in wrong.
- Well, I don't know.
I think she knows how to use a phone.
I'm just saying, she
could've typed it in wrong.
- Same shit.
- How is that possible?
Joyce has this telemarketer
job. Always on the phone.
Mike won't stop whining about it.
Yeah, but this phone's been
busy for, what, three days now?
That's not Joyce.
No way. Something's wrong.
She's right.
It can't be just
coincidence. It can't be.
Whatever's happening in Lenora
is connected to all of this.
I'm sure of it.
But Vecna can't hurt them.
Not if he's dead.
We have to go back in there.
Back to the Upside Down.
- Whoa, no, no, no. What?
- Nope.
- Let's think this through.
- What is there to think through?
- We barely made it out of there.
- Yeah, because we weren't prepared.
But this time, we will be.
We'll get weapons and protection.
We'll go through the gate, we'll
find his lair, and we'll kill him.
Or he'll kill us.
The only reason you survived
is because he wanted you to.
- He's not scared of us.
- And for good reason.
We were wrong about Vecna. Henry. One.
Sorry, what are we calling him now?
- One.
- Vecna.
- Henry.
- Right.
We've learned something
new about Vecna/Henry/One.
He's a number like Eleven,
only a sick, evil, male,
child-murdering version of
her with really bad skin.
But my... my point is,
he's super powerful.
Could turn us inside out
with a snap of his fingers.
It's not a fair fight.
Then why fight fair?
You're right. He's like Eleven.
But that gives us an upper hand.
We know Eleven's strengths.
And weaknesses.
Weaknesses?
When El remote-travels,
she goes into this sort
of trance-like state.
I bet the same is true of Vecna.
That would explain what
he was doing in that attic.
Exactly. When he
attacks his next victim,
I'll bet you he's back in that
attic, physical body defenseless.
Defenseless? What
about the army of bats?
True. We'll have to
find a way past them.
Distract them somehow.
- And, uh, how do we do that, exactly?
- No idea.
But once they're gone,
he doesn't stand a chance.
It'll be like slaying
sleeping Dracula in his coffin.
That all sounds good in theory,
but there is no pattern
to Vecna's killings.
Not one that I can decipher.
We don't know when he's
going to attack next.
- Don't even know who he's going to attack.
- Yeah, we do.
I can still feel him.
I'm still marked.
Cursed.
I ditch Kate Bush,
I draw his focus back to me.
Max.
You can't.
He'll kill you.
I survived before.
I can survive again.
I just need to keep him busy long enough
so that you guys can
get into that attic.
Then you can chop his head off.
Stab him in the heart. Blow him up
with some explosive Dustin cooks up.
I honestly don't care how you
put this asshole in his grave.
Just...
... whatever it is...
whatever you do...
try not to miss.
Bam.
Durak.
Son of a bitch!
Sayonara!
Oh God! Oh God!
Son of a bitch!
- You okay? All right?
- Yeah.
- You okay?
- Okay? I'm great! Whoo!
Oh, nothing like a little prison escape
to get your day started, am I right?
We're not out of the woods yet.
My people do not take kindly to
escapes. They'll be hunting us.
Yeah, well, we aren't exactly
planning on sticking around.
- Where's the plane you came in on?
- That plane? Um, that crashed.
- Crashed?
- His fault.
A word of warning.
That man is more slippery
than an eel dipped in baby oil.
I wouldn't trust a
word out of his mouth.
My tongue. My tongue!
I... I can't feel my tongue.
We need to get out of
here, back to the States.
Can you get us to another plane?
Now?
You're asking for Yuri's help
after dragging him through
miles of shit tunnel?
I could have told you we are
going wrong way hours ago.
You Neanderthal...
Watch your mouth, or
I am gonna take this,
I'm gonna rub it along
the bottom of my shoe,
and I'm gonna jam it down your throat.
Well, go ahead!
But then you'll never make
it out of my country alive.
So you can get us out.
For a glass of water and hot steam bath
and five-inch stack of American dollars,
Yuri will fly you to moon.
You make another demand,
you double-crossing mudak,
I'll decorate the roof of
this van with your brains.
Why so angry, comrade?
Rough couple of days for you, I'm sure.
But now you are free.
Everything works out.
Happy ending for everybody.
No?
For you, that will very much
depend on how you answer. Comrade.
Will you take us to America?
Yes?
Or no?
Check this out. The War Zone.
I've been there once. It's huge.
They got everything you need for, uh...
well, killing things, basically.
You think fake Rambo
has enough guns there?
Is that a grenade? I mean,
how is any of this legal?
Well, lucky for us it is, so...
This... This place is just
far enough outside of Hawkins.
As long as we steer clear of main roads,
we oughta be able to avoid
cops and, uh, angry hicks.
If we're trying to avoid angry hicks,
maybe we shouldn't go to some
store called the War Zone.
Normally, I'd agree,
but we need the weapons.
- So I think it's worth the risk.
- Me too.
But is it worth the time? It'll
take all day to bike there and back.
- Who said anything about bikes?
- You got some car we don't know about?
It's not exactly a car, Steve.
And it's not exactly mine,
but, uh... it'll do.
Hey, Red, uh, you got a ski mask
or a bandanna, something like that?
That was suffocating.
Go! Come on.
Where'd you learn how to do this?
Well, when the other dads
were teaching their kids
how to fish or play ball,
my old man was teaching
me how to hot-wire.
Now, I swore to myself I
wouldn't wind up like he did,
but now I'm wanted for murder,
and soon, grand theft auto.
So, uh, I'm really living
up to that Munson name.
Eddie, I'm not sure I love
the idea of you driving.
Oh, I'm just starting this
sucker. Harrington's got her.
Don't ya, big boy?
What the hell?
Hey! Open this door!
- Hey!
- They locked the door!
Shit! Go.
It's just a car. Everybody,
hang on to something!
Oh my God! Let's go! Let's go!
Drive, Steve! Drive!
Go, go, go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Shit, they look pissed.
It's not every day you lose your
house and car in one fell swoop.
Hold on! Hold on!
Them!
Stop 'em! God bless it!
Okay.
My friends. I saw them.
You told me they were safe.
- They are not safe.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, okay.
Uh, just give us a second, please.
Please.
Okay, okay, first... first things first.
We're not gonna let anything
happen to your friends, okay, kiddo?
I will personally make sure of that.
Did... Did you see where they were?
They were at... They
were at Max's house.
They're planning to kill him.
To kill Henry.
Okay. Okay.
This... Does this Max have a last name?
Max... Max Mayfield.
Okay. So here's what's gonna happen.
I have people in Hawkins, and I'm
gonna send some to Max Mayfield.
- And they will stop him...
- Her.
Stop her. And the rest of them
from whatever foolish, although
well-intentioned, mission
that they're attempting, all right?
No. No, do not send your men.
Send me.
Your friends are not prepared
for this fight, Eleven.
And neither are you.
You must understand,
when One kills, he doesn't simply kill.
He consumes.
He takes everything from his victims.
Everything they are and
everything they ever will be.
Their memories, their abilities.
And we do not know where
he's been these lost years.
But if he has survived this long,
we can only assume
that he has grown in strength.
To underestimate him,
to act rashly,
would be very dangerous.
I don't want to upset you, Eleven.
What you've accomplished is
nothing short of a miracle.
You came to me broken.
And you've learned to walk again.
But if you want to stop One,
you will need to do more than walk.
You will need to do more than run.
You will need to fly.
And you're not ready.
My friends need me.
I've stopped him once. I will again.
I'm sorry. You can't.
It's impossible.
Nothing's impossible.
I can call Stinson. She's
got connections at Nellis.
That's two hours away.
And if we hustle, I'll bet we can
be in Hawkins before nightfall.
That would be a grave mistake.
Waiting would be an
even greater mistake.
What if One makes his move
before we've had a
chance to throw a punch?
Then what is the point of all this?
That's a risk we're
going to have to take.
We pushed her before
and look what happened.
She lifted a 10,000-pound
tank into the goddamn air.
You don't understand
what he's capable of!
Maybe you're right. Or maybe
you are overestimating him.
Either way, doesn't matter
because this is not our choice.
We agreed this was
not gonna be a prison.
We'll show her what this is,
what we can offer,
and then it is her choice
whether she wants to stay or go.
Right, Doc?
You may not agree with it,
but here she is, standing before us,
making a choice.
You're sure you wanna do this?
Okay. Pack your things,
say your goodbyes.
- How's it handle?
- Not half bad.
Considering that this is a...
house.
♪ Yesterday mornin' ♪
♪ They let me know you were gone... ♪
Yeah, it's...
it's silly, but I... I've actually...
I always had this dream that I'd
have this really... really big family.
I'm talking, like, uh,
a full brood of Harringtons.
Like, five, six kids.
- Six?
- Yeah. Six little nuggets.
Three girls, three boys.
And... and every summer, I
figured all of us Harringtons,
we would pack into something like this
and... just see the country.
You know, the Rockies, Grand Canyon,
maybe Yellowstone.
End up in some beachside
town in California.
Spend a week parked in the sand.
Learn how to surf or something.
That sounds nice.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Well, uh, except for the six-kid part.
That sounds like a total nightmare.
If only I had some practice.
All right. Fair.
That's fair.
♪ Oh, I've seen fire
and I've seen rain ♪
♪ I've seen sunny days ♪
♪ That I thought would never end ♪
♪ I've seen lonely times ♪
♪ When I could not find a friend ♪
Hey.
♪ But I always thought ♪
♪ That I'd see you again... ♪
So I've been thinking,
two of the three of Vecna's victims
were seeing Ms. Kelley, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
So I figure there's a good chance
Vecna cursed another
one of her students.
We go back to her office.
We read all of her files.
Look for mentions of headaches,
nosebleeds, nightmares.
- We identify his most likely next victim.
- Lucas.
- We stake out his house...
- Lucas, stop.
We don't have time
for any of that, okay?
And even if we did,
even if your plan did work,
we'd be putting a
total stranger at risk.
A stranger who has no idea
what they're up against.
I do.
He uses my memories against me.
But... only my darkest memories.
- Same with Chrissy and Fred, right?
- Right.
It's like he only sees
the darkness in us.
So, I'll just run in
the opposite direction.
Run to the light.
And maybe he won't be
able to find me there.
Now, how exactly do
you plan on doing this?
I'm not sure.
But it's my mind.
Not his, right?
So I should be able
to control where I am.
I just need to... push him away.
Find a happy memory and hide there.
Hide in the light.
You got a memory in mind?
Yeah.
It was a time when I was
the happiest.
Was I there?
That's presumptuous of you.
But yeah.
You might've been there.
Okay, but the second you start to lift,
I'm calling in Kate Bush.
- All right?
- Okay.
- Deal.
Heh, come on. This way.
If I get a whiff of any
funny business, smuggler...
I will not hesitate to kill you.
In fact... I am just looking
for a reason. Understand?
Are you a parrot, cop? You
keep repeating the same thing.
You were trapped in a
cell with this dull man
and you didn't take
opportunity to smother him.
Beautiful, yes?
Please tell me this
is another poor joke.
You said you had a plane.
- A plane!
- No, no, no.
I... I told you I could fly you home.
And Katinka can fly
you home, little bird.
She was named Katinka
after my first lover.
Katinka also had very
beautiful, very round buttocks.
Uh, mu... much like this.
This cannot fly us to America.
Why not?
As long as winds are not too strong
and your military friends
do not shoot us out of sky,
we can make it to the coast.
There, while we refuel,
we skin dip in ice-cold
water and wash off this muck.
Then we fly her rest of the way.
Happy ending.
Okay, what is the furthest
Katinka has ever flown?
For me, she is still a virgin.
Uh, not real Katinka. Goodness, no.
That Katinka, no.
But this Katinka, pretty much unspoiled.
But I'm sure she will
soar when given a chance.
She just need little tune-up.
- I did warn you, Jim.
- Okay.
Should I shoot him now? Or later?
What about Owens?
He... He's gotta have contacts
or spies here that could help us.
Can we do that?
Can we make a call to the States?
Yes, hello, miss.
I'd like to place a call to the
United States. A very sick relative.
Correct. Yes... The number is...
- The number?
- It's 775...
... 305...
... 3450.
Da, spasibo.
- What are you doing?
- How exactly do you think this works?
They will make the call for us,
and then they will call us back.
How long's that gonna take?
Five minutes. Five hours.
Five days. Who knows?
And when we do get the call,
assume the KGB will
be on the other line,
listening to everything you say.
So,
I suggest talking in code.
Say the wrong thing
and they will be on
us like flies on shit.
Welcome to the Soviet Union.
So much for avoiding angry hicks.
Let's be... fast.
- Yep.
- Definitely.
- How many of these do you think we need?
- Five or six.
What are you gonna do? Stand and gawk?
Shut up.
Ah!
Jesus, you scared me.
Whoa. You gonna mace me with that?
If it keeps you in line, yeah.
See? Not so scary.
Robin. Robin!
Who's that?
Someone from band.
How much is this?
$120.99, but I'll throw in
20 rounds of buckshot for ya.
Hey, can I see this
real pretty .357, please?
Sure thing.
- Here you go, son.
- Thank you.
Nancy Wheeler.
Wouldn't expect to find you here.
Yeah, well, it's just... scary times.
I'm... sorry about Chrissy.
Want my advice?
Shotguns are not good for much of
anything past killing small birds.
I mean, they got power, sure,
but not much range.
And that's just gonna force
you into close-range combat,
then someone can just grab
that barrel like this...
... and redirect it.
Well, you look nervous.
Like I said,
scary times.
Now, your brother, he, uh...
is he here with you, by chance?
Mike?
Mike.
No.
I only ask because he's...
he's in Hellfire, isn't he?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- What about his friends?
They here with you?
Would you let go?
Let go.
What the hell is taking so long?
- What happened?
- Gotta go.
- Your old friends are here.
- Shit!
- Let's go! Let's go!
- I'm going! I'm going! Sit down!
Should be up on our right.
There's nothing out here.
Mmm. We there already?
- Already? It's been nine hours.
- It's gotta be around here somewhere.
What are we looking for, my dudes?
- Some sort of facility.
- A fence. A building.
Any signs of life would be nice.
Since when did we decide Nina was
a building and not a small woman?
Sounds like a small woman to me.
It's not a small woman.
Small woman out in this
desert would be hard to see.
- How is he still high?
- Sure you got your measurements right?
Yes, they're right.
- You're 100%, right?
- Yes.
Maybe latitude and longitude are wrong.
- Are you really questioning Suzie?
- She's a genius, Jonathan.
- Even geniuses make mistakes.
- Well, she didn't.
If that small woman is small enough,
she could fit behind a small tree.
Stop! Just...
- Ouch.
- What are you doing?
I am stopping us
before we get more lost.
- Give me the coordinates.
- Um, okay.
Longitude is 116 degrees,
five minutes, and 17...
Slow down. Slow down.
Nina!
Nina.
Nina?
Nina!
Holy macaroni.
All right. You just go straight
down. Like, straight... straight...
Right on the money, as I said.
- It just doesn't make sense.
- Yo, dudes!
My dudes!
Jesus Christ.
Come check this shit out!
What is it?
Gotta see it to believe it, my dudes!
Come on! Hurry!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go! Pronto!
Okay.
So no small woman named Nina.
But you said any signs
of life, am I right?
- Right.
- Well,
these are no regular
tire tracks, brochachos.
I mean, look at the
tread on these monsters.
They're fatties. And
you know what that means.
Military.
We gotta go.
Well, I wouldn't do it if I
didn't think she was ready.
But either way, I don't think
we have any other choice.
- Do you?
- No, I don't.
Yeah.
- It might take me some time though.
- Just... As fast as you can.
It's gonna take us two hours
to get to Nellis as it is.
And, Ellen, one more favor.
Can you send somebody over
to a Max Mayfield's house?
There are some kids there that
just need looking after, okay?
Ellen? Hello?
Sam? Hello?
Why the long face, Doc?
We just wanna talk.
No! Wait!
No! No!
What...
You can't leave, Eleven.
Where is Dr. Owens?
Dr. Owens had a change of heart.
I know you wish to go to him,
and there's nothing I can do to stop you
from forcing open that door.
But if my men hear you coming,
they will kill him.
And alone, you will never find your way
out of this desert to your friends.
Here's what we're going to do.
You and I are going to
complete our work together.
And when I decide that you are ready,
we will return to Hawkins, together.
Papa and daughter.
Why are you doing this?
Because there's no other choice.
There is a choice.
Only one that is right.
And you make the right choices?
I try.
Did you make the right choice with Mama?
Four-fifty.
Your mother was sick, Eleven.
She was a danger to
herself and to others.
She brought a gun into the
hospital. She killed a man.
Hospital?
No.
A prison.
Everything I have done
was for your own good.
For your own protection.
And Henry?
You kept Henry in that lab.
With the children.
Was that for our good?
Was that a right choice?
I had no idea what Henry would do.
I cared for you.
I loved you. I loved all of you.
Even Henry?
Yes.
I was trying to help Henry,
to understand him. Yes.
Yes, I cared for him.
Even after what... what he did?
Yes.
Because I knew I had failed him.
So this morning,
you said you believed he was
always alive in the darkness.
Is that why I was
searching the darkness?
Was I looking for him? For Henry?
No. No.
We were focused on the Soviets.
You knew that.
"Papa does not tell the truth."
Henry said that.
And now you trust Henry?
Henry, who's manipulated
you like some puppet?
You are the one who
released him from his prison.
You.
And now you are angry with yourself
and you're taking your anger out on me
and you're risking everything.
No.
No, you.
You have risked everything!
You have lied!
You made me look for him!
The gate.
The Mind Flayer.
So many dead.
And all because of you.
Because you could not stop.
You could not let him go.
I came here to try and
understand who I was.
To see if I...
if I was the monster.
Papa!
And now I know the truth.
It is not me.
It is you.
You
are the monster.
I am going to open that door,
and I am going to leave
with Dr. Owens.
If you try to stop me, I will kill you.
You'll soon see the truth, Eleven.
Ah!
Is this legal?
Actually, I think it's a felony.
Right.
But it guarantees one thing.
I won't miss.
- How's she feeling?
- Light. But durable.
Deadly.
But reliable.
Hear me now.
There will be no more retreating...
from Eddie the Banished.
Hey, you're really ready for bat-tle.
You get it?
"Bat-tle."
B-A-T.
No?
I thought I had a good one.
What are you doing?
You son of a bitch!
No wedgies! No wedgies!
Never change,
Dustin Henderson.
Promise me?
I wasn't planning on it.
Good.
- Good.
Hey, Sinclairs.
How are those, uh...
those spears coming on?
Flip that damn thumb around.
What?
It's too loose, Lucas.
This isn't a basketball game
where they blow the whistle
when your shoes fall off.
Okay, okay, for the record,
my shoes never fell off.
Okay, for the record,
it's kinda hard for
your shoes to fall off
when you're riding the bench.
Yet, for some reason,
you show up to every game.
Mmm, except the one that mattered.
Plus, Mom and Dad forced me.
Bull. Mom and Dad can't
force you to do shit.
Well, even though you're
a bench-riding loser,
you're still my brother.
Just the facts.
- It just doesn't make sense.
- What doesn't make sense?
That was Dan Shelter. He
graduated, like, two years ago.
- So?
- So he's in college.
Which means he was
visiting on spring break.
Fast Times was returned,
like, I don't know, a week ago?
Right? Unless she's got some
horndog brother we don't know about.
Which is possible.
Or she's just really
into Judge Reinhold?
- Steve.
- Nah.
- What?
- I don't care.
I don't understand why you do either
with everything that's going on.
Honestly, this feels like a perfect time
for that little pull
of the rug because...
in the face of the world ending,
the stakes of my love life
feel spectacularly low.
Yeah. I mean, I get you there,
but... I still have hope.
- Not everything has a happy ending.
- Yeah, yeah, believe me, I know.
I'm not talking about failed romance.
I just...
I have this terrible,
gnawing feeling that...
it might not work out for us this time.
You think we shouldn't be doing this?
I think we're mad fools,
the lot of us, but...
... but if we don't stop him, who will?
We have to try, right?
Yeah.
To killing Vecna.
Slash Henry.
Slash One.
It's only a precaution, Eleven.
I never intend to activate it.
I very much hope
our fighting has come to an end.
Shh.
I know.
You're angry with me.
But it was the only way.
The best way.
- What's going on?
- It's Sullivan.
They found us.
Go, go, go!
Three! Two! One!
- Go to the back!
- Get moving!
- Move out!
- Go!
- Get 'em out of here!
- No more time!
Evacuate now!
Move!
Steady! Fire!
Eleven, we have to go.
- What is happening?
- They've come to kill you.
Evacuate immediately. Please proceed...
- Clear.
- Clear!
Quarter and search by twos.
Hicks, take the upper level.
Yes, sir.
Sir?
We found something
you're gonna wanna see.
Well, well.
And what happened here?
Hmm?
Are Mommy and Daddy fighting?
Okay.
Let's try this again, shall we?
Where's the girl?
Where do you think you're going, Doc?
- Why don't you give 'em some lead?
- I got it.
Down he goes.
Victor-Two-Sierra, this
is Charlie-Lima-Golf.
Do you copy, over?
Victor-Two-Sierra, I copy, over.
We've got the target in our sights.
Requesting permission
to take the shot, over.
Jack, you don't have to do this.
It's over, Sam.
Wait! Wait! Wait! I
can put her in a coma.
A medically induced coma.
We have the drugs. We
can do it right here.
And we'll see if... if
these murders keep happening.
If you're right, the killing ends,
and you can pull the plug on her.
In fact, I'll do it myself.
But if you're wrong about this,
God, are we gonna need her.
Jack.
Don't do this.
I'm begging you.
Take it.
You son of a bitch!
No! You son of a bitch!
Green light. Light her up.
Civvies. Five o'clock.
The hell?
- There she is! There she is!
- Where?
- On the ground!
- What are those dudes doing on the ground?
- Is that blood, man?
- Shit.
Victor-Two-Sierra, we've
got a civvy headed our way.
Ignore it. Just take out the girl.
Copy that. Ignore the
civvy. Take the shot.
Found ya.
- Hell are you doing? Hold her steady!
- I don't know, man. Something's wrong!
Jesus Christ.
Holy shit!
Shit!
I'm losing her!
- Shit!
- Shit! I can't! I can't hold it!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
Eleven!
Eleven.
Oh, Mike.
It's really you?
It's me.
- I'm here.
- Okay.
Everyone's here.
Shit. Shit. Shit.
Oh shit.
Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Shit!
Eleven.
You... Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- Okay.
Hey, guys. We gotta go.
We gotta get you outta here.
Papa.
Eleven.
I want you to know
I'm proud of you.
So very proud.
You
are my family.
My child.
I've only ever
wanted to help you.
To protect you.
Everything I did,
I did for you.
I need you to understand.
Please tell me you understand.
Please.
Goodbye, Papa.
- We need to get to Hawkins.
- I know. And we will.
But we need to get you somewhere
safe. Gonna be people behind us.
No, Mike, we need to
get to Hawkins tonight.
We'll never make it.
That's over 2,000 miles.
We need to find a way.
If we don't, they are going to die.
Who's gonna die?
El, who's gonna die?
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -